（忆往昔）
- 你好 - 鲍比·辛格吗
- Hello? - Bobby Singer?
我的医生是个怪物
My surgeon is a monster.
求你快来苏福尔斯综合医院
Please get your ass here to Sioux Falls General.
他们就像易形者
They're like shapeshifters.
只是更爱吃人肉
only a lot more into eating folk.
而且没有东西能杀了他们
And nothing can kill 'em.
还有什么别的吗
Anything else?
有 他们流出的是黑色的胶状物
Yep. They bleed black goo.
你好 萨姆
Hi, Sam.
你好 迪恩
Hi, Dean.
咒语只能维持数日
Spell only lasts for a few days.
你不想说出的那些心事不会自行消失
The stuff you don't talk about doesn't just go away.
那你究竟想说什么
Well, then what the hell are you talking about?
我是指你不想说的那件心事
I'm talking about whatever you're not telling me about.
我们可以交心的 不是吗
We're good, right?
我们没问题
We're good.
（如今）
这样行吗
You sure about this?
相信我
Trust me.
早上好 梅根
Good morning… Megan.
你这件衣服真漂亮
That is a really, really pretty dress.
谢谢夸奖 这件衣服有年头了
Thank you. It's vintage.
穿在你身上显得很新
Well, it looks new on you.
你嘴真甜 先生
Aren't you sweet, sir?
叫我迪恩就行
Call me Dean.
有什么需要我帮忙 迪恩
How can I help you today, Dean?
我在这家银行没有账户
Well, I don't actually have an account at this bank,
你能不能想法子
but I was wondering if there was any way…
把这张换成零钱
I could get change for that?
我可以专门为你…
I think I can make an exception…
搞点特殊
just for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
你想换成什么面值的 迪恩
How do you want it, Dean?
要不还是改天吧
Well, I'm gonna have to take a rain check…
把你们的钱都交出来
And all your money.
把手举起来 把手举起来
Hands in the air! Hands in the air!
你们的钱保过险了
Your money's insured,
所以就别想逞英雄了
so no heroes, okay?
进去吧你
Get in there.
准备好了吗
You ready?
好了
Yep.
[邪恶力量 第7季第6集]
好了 切特
Okay, Chet.
来尝尝毒树之果的滋味如何
Let's see how you like a little fruit of the poison tree.
那不只是个法律术语吗
Isn't that just a legal expression?
想得倒美
You're gonna wish it was.
好了
Oaky.
跟圣水的滋味有点像
Similar finish to holy water,
不像岩盐那么苦
not as bitter as rock salt.
我最喜欢的两具肉身还好吗
And how are my two favorite meat-sicles?
他还喘气儿呢
Is he still sucking air?
怎么打都死不了
Greatest hits didn't do the trick.
就差没用二流的音乐折磨他了
I'm down to B-sides and deep cuts.
你最好快点找出办法
Well, you better figure out something quick.
那个什么巫师在他身上施的咒
That whammy that witch dude put on him.
只能撑几天而已
is only gonna last for a few days.
一旦他恢复元气
He gets his spinach back,
想拦住他 就只能拿汽车砸了
we're gonna end up having to drop a car on him just to stop him.
其实
Actually…
埃德加从车底下爬出来了
Edgar walked away from that car.
他毫发无损
He's fine.
虽说他有点生你们的气 但…
Well, he is a little pissed at you, but …
你们还不知道吗
You didn't know?
闭上你的臭嘴吧
Why don't you shut your caketrap?
鲍比
Bobby…
你用了这么多招 他还是不肯开口吗
You've been using all this stuff and he still won't talk?
来了您呐 教练
Huddle over, coach?
你怎么找到我们的
How'd you find us?
很简单
It was easy.
我用了图像识别软件
I used pattern-recognition software.
还有基础启发性算法 查到了你们的化名
and a basic heuristic algorithm to track your known aliases.
很好
Great.
怕什么来什么 还是个高智商怪物
Just what we need … a Mensa monster.
好了
All right.
咱们从头说起
Let's just start with the start.
你怎么知道我们的化名
Where'd you get our aliases?
从你们穿风衣的朋友那儿知道的
From your trench-coated friend, obviously.
我们在「小卡营」驻扎的时候
When we were all nestled in at Camp Cass,
下载了他脑子里的全部资料
kind of got the full download.
我们就有这本事
That's just how we do.
那你为什么要告诉我们呢 切特
So why are you talking to us, Chet?
你又不傻
You're not dumb.
你为什么要泄露国家机密
Why you spilling state secrets?
因为我不怕你们
'Cause I'm not scared of you.
你们阻挡不了我
You can't stop me.
对我们谁都造不成威胁
You can't stop any of us.
我们有不死之身 你们这群傻帽
We can't be killed, you stupid little chewtoys.
你们现在该担心的不是我吧
You are aware that I'm the least of your concerns, right?
看来你们还没看今天的新闻
You haven't watched the news today, have you?
此前被认定为死亡的两人
The two men, who up until today were presumed dead,
封锁出口 大开杀戒
locked the doors and opened fire,
无人生还
leaving no survivors.
加州对萨姆及迪恩·温彻斯特
Sam and Dean Winchester are now the subjects.
展开了全面通缉
of a manhunt throughout the state of California.
你们俩今早挺忙啊
Busy morning, you two?
那俩混蛋变成咱们的模样
Those sons of bitches xeroxed us.
他们是怎么做到的
But I don't understand how.
我不知道
I don't know.
可能他们有人在医院碰了你们
Maybe one of 'em touched you at the hospital.
他们用了头发
It was the hair!
从旅馆淋浴下水口很容易搞到你们的DNA
Not too hard to lift some DNA out of a motel shower drain, guys!
那样就能克隆人吗
You can copy people like that?
真赞
Awesome.
他们到底打算干什么
Well, what is their plan, exactly?
逼咱们
Squeeze us.
把咱们变成全美关注的焦点
Turn us into the most wanted men in America.
好吧 那就别怪咱们了
All right. Well, that settles it.
要是找到那俩混球 就亲手宰了他们
We find these ass monkeys, and we kill them ourselves.
等等
Wait a sec.
全国所有的执法机关
Every form of law enforcement in the country.
今早都见着你们的丑样了
has seen your ugly mugs this morning.
没错 那还有啥必要躲躲藏藏的
Exactly. So what's the point in trying to hide?
总比伸出脖子找死强
Better than sticking your fool neck out.
那些家伙比你们狡猾多了
These things are smarter than you.
喂 鲍比 这话可不好听
Geez, Bobby, don't sugarcoat it.
你们根本不知道怎么杀它们
You don't have a clue how to kill 'em.
或是拖延时间 而你们的计划是什么
or slow 'em down, and your plan is, what?
正面交锋 算了吧
Go right at 'em? Genius.
它们装成我们的样子 鲍比
They're wearing our faces, Bobby.
这笔账必须算
This is personal.
我赞成迪恩的说法
I'm with Dean here.
好吧 如果你们要做傻事
Well, if you're gonna be stupid,
最好是放机灵点儿
you might as well be smart about it.
你们得去见一个名叫弗兰克·德弗罗的家伙
You need to see a fella named Frank Devereaux.
他是谁
Who's he?
傻子加疯子
He's a jackass and a lunatic,
当年在休伦港他欠我个人情
but he owes me one, from back in Port Huron.
与此同时
In the meantime,
我要接着对付那个话痨
I'll keep working on chatty Cathy here,
看看能不能找出杀死他的办法
See if I can figure out what makes him die.
老样子
The usual?
Rhymes with sing-songs.
你们有没有蛋白棒
You guys sell protein bars?
有
Yeah.
不过 我要去后面拿
But it's in … it's in the back, though.
请稍等一会儿
Just, uh, give me a second.
行 谢了
Sure. Thanks.
那个收银员肯定认出我了
Pretty sure the cashier just made me.
开车
Drive.
妈的
Hell.
谢谢
Thanks.
我是莫瑞斯特工 这位是瓦伦提
Special agent Morris. This is special agent Valente.
先生们
Gentlemen.
我听说温彻斯特兄弟很忙啊
These Winchester boys are keeping busy, I hear.
这算啥 杀人越货旅行团吗
What is this, some type of psycho road trip?
第二家银行了 外加便利店
The second bank, plus that convenience store?
他们几天前还是死人呢
Couple of days ago, they were dead.
我们不比你了解更多
We know about what you know.
失陪
Excuse me.
真正的连环杀手
Actual serial killers.
有案子就有大量的文书工作
Crime spree means paperwork. Lots of it.
有你忙的了
Which you'll be doing.
该出发了
We gotta go.
有个加油站发现了他们的行踪
Winchesters spotted at a gas n' sip.
距离这里有一千英里左右
It's about a thousand miles from here.
太快了吧
That's fast.
飞过去的吧
Must have flown.
要么就是坐蝙蝠战车
That or batmobile.
你确定找对地方了吗
You sure this is the right place?
确定
Yeah.
弗兰克 在吗
Frank, you in there?
弗兰克
Frank?
弗兰克 有人吗
Frank, anybody here?
喂
Hello?
有人在家吗
Anybody home?
瞧啊
Well, well.
蜘蛛抓到飞虫了
Spider caught some flies.
我勒个去
Well, I'll be darned.
是大白天作案的杀人狂啊
Psycho butch and sundance.
CNN正在播你们的新闻
You're on CNN right now.
不不 那不是我们
No, no, t-that's not us.
我知道 不可能是
I know. Can't be.
除非你们有传送器
Unless you had a teleporter.
你们有传送器吗
Do you have a teleporter?
没有 先生
No…Sir.
当然没有
We don't.
沉痛哀悼你们有对疯子二重身啊
Well, my condolences on the doppelgangers.
那么 谁派你们来的 国安局的蠢货
Now, who sent you? NSA? The feeb?
畸形儿基金会
March of dimes?
是鲍比·辛格
Uh, Bobby Singer sent us.
当我没说
Or not. Who?
他说你可以帮忙
H-he said you could help.
你还记得当年休伦港的事吗
He said you owed him, from Port Huron.
有人救了你一命
Guy saves your life one time,
然后呢 一辈子都欠着他了吗
and, what, you owe him the rest of yours?
没错 一般来说都是这样的
That's usually how it works, yeah.
没错
Oh, yeah.
我知道鲍比总搞些神神鬼鬼的事儿
I know that Bobby's into that magic hooey,
事实是
but truth is,
政府研究克隆人好多年了
The government have been cloning people for years.
没准轮到你们头上了
Guess it was just your turn in the barrel.
- 其实… - 别 听他说
- Well, actually … - forget it. He's rolling.
你们的克隆人忙得很啊
Yours have been busy beavers.
眼看着你们就成了第二号通缉犯
You're number two on the most wanted list.
自堂娜·萨默（美国黑人女歌手）以来爬得最快了
Quickest climb up the charts since Donna Summer.
那你觉得我们该怎么做
So, what do you think we should do?
这个时节去古巴不错
Cuba's nice this time of year.
不 我们不打算躲起来
No, we're not hiding.
他从来就这么蠢吗
Is he always this stupid?
听着 我们要留下来好好教训那两个家伙
Look, we got to stick around and kick a couple asses.
只需要你帮我们远离牢房
So, we just need you to get us further off the grid,
同时又能自由行动
but keep us on the board.
好吧 第一件事就是清除以前所有的化名
Well, first thing we got to do is wipe all your old aliases.
不能太高调
No more rock shoutouts.
从现在开始就叫汤姆和约翰·史密斯
It's Tom and John Smith from now on.
不能用卡
And no plastic.
只用现金
Cash only.
要非常频繁 而且不定期地
And change your phones on a very frequent.
换手机 明白吗
non-schedule schedule, you understand?
还有 尽量避开政府有权调用的
Oh, and try to stay out of view of the 200 million cameras.
两亿个摄像头 明白吗
that the government has access to, 'kay?
两亿
200 million?
老大哥（代指政府）嘛
Big brother,
他的眼睛可多了 朋友们
he has many eyeballs, my friend.
只要看到一个地方
You see a place that even looks like.
可能有保安系统
it can afford security,
二话不说就赶紧撤
You just ease on down the road.
这个
This…
是你的笔记本 对吧
This is your laptop, right?
是啊 这是我的
Yeah. That's mine.
我靠 喂 嘿
What … gee … hey …
你这是干嘛呢
What are you … what was that?!
我想我要谢谢你
Thank you, I guess.
没问题 你欠我五千块 现金
No problem. You owe me five grand, cash.
- 啥 - 啥
- What? - What?
你还想到购物中心去货比三家吗
Unless you wanna go comparison shop at the mall,
小可爱们
sweet cheeks.
替我向条子问好
Say hi to the cops for me.
好了
Okay.
我们来弄张新的证件照
Let's blue steel you up some new I.D.,
两位史密斯先生
Mr. and Mr. Smith.
再来一次 来吧 再来一次
Do it again! Come on, do it again!
你打算就这样在清晨抚摸我
So you're just gonna touch me in the morning,
然后转身离去吗
then just walk away?
你怎么还能说话
Are you still talkin'?
你还没玩厌吗
Aren't you sick of this yet?
你流的血
You bleed.
像是黑色的…鼻涕
Black…snot, sure,
不过你会流血你就会死
but you bleed, you can die.
行啊 小伙子 随你怎么说
Sure, sport, whatever you say.
怎么不再试试酸呢
Try the acid again, why don't you?
可怜的家伙 你束手无策了
Poor sap. You're stumped.
消停一下 话痨
Give it a rest, mouthy.
你觉得一旦咒语失效
How long you think these'll hold.
这些东西能撑多久
once the spell wears off, hmm?
时间不多了 老头子
Tick tock, old man.
我会好好享用你的
I'm gonna really enjoy eating you,
连帽子也吃了
right down to that hat.
我说了闭嘴
I said shut up.
接着我要吃了所有…
And then I'm gonna eat everyone…
你打过招呼的人
you ever said hello to.
哇塞
Hot damn.
这招不错
Well, that's somethin'.
我标记了你们的克隆人犯事的城市
I marked all the towns your stunt doubles hit.
这样你可以找出规律
so you can see the pattern.
好的 非常好
All right, great.
是什么样的规律呢
Um, so, what is the pattern?
不知道啊 哥们 我看不出
No clue, man. I can't see it.
看上去是随机的
Seems random.
专家意见
Little tip from a pro …
你们的邪恶分身不可能随机
There is no such thing as a random series.
挑地方抢劫杀人的
of robbery murders by your evil twins.
给自己吃点兴奋剂 再好好研究一下
Well, have yourself some uppers and look at that some more.
祝你好运
Good luck.
谢谢 弗兰克
Thanks, Frank.
谢什么 把你们送上死路
For what? Sending you to your death?
你们的克隆人想办法被拍下来
Your doubles want to be on "candid camera, "
好让你们置身水深火热之中
put you in the line of fire.
换了我就低调点
Now, I'd lay low,
因为我热爱生活和它道不尽的神秘感
'cause I love life and its infinite mysteries.
你们俩想当傻瓜 没关系
But you two want to be dumb, that's fine.
至少也把你们的车扔掉
At least have the common sense to ditch your car.
不好意思 什么
Uh, excuse me. What?
你们的克隆人
Your doublemints …
他们开的车和外面那辆一样
They're using a car just like the one outside.
（杀手二人组仍然在逃）
搞什么…
What the…
你来这搞什么鬼
What the hell are you doing here?
你真是魅力无穷 鲍比
You're all charm, Bobby.
我的心理医生也一直这么跟我说
So my therapist keeps telling me.
你怎么找到我的
How'd you find me?
我是个警察 记得吗
I'm a cop, remember?
你不打算邀请我进去吗
You gonna invite me in?
你可能不会想进来
Well, you may not want me to.
我抓了个食人怪放楼下了
I got one of the big mouths downstairs.
那我不到楼下去就是
So I won't go downstairs.
我…
I, uh…
我想来谢谢你
I wanted to come thank you.
谢谢我
Thank me?
是的…
Well, yeah…
因为商店里写有
Seeing as they were fresh out of.
「感谢你把我从吃肝脏的医生手里救出来」
"Thanks for saving me from liver-eating surgeon"
的卡片卖光了
cards at the store.
那个啊 那是我的工作
Oh, that. Just doing my job,
还没工资
which nobody pays me for.
是这样
Right.
你最近怎么样 鲍比
How you doing, Bobby?
我很好
I'm fine.
对生命充满感激
Every day is a gift.
你的房子刚被烧毁了
Your house just burned down.
你也看见了 我还没露宿街头
As you can see, I got a roof over me.
鲍比
Bobby!
就允许别人哪怕善待你五分钟好吗
Let someone be nice to you for five minutes?
好啊
Okay.
但是别太好了
But not too nice.
我不能变软了
I can't be going soft.
当然不会
'Course not.
我会做饭
I can cook.
八九不离十吧
Ish. You know?
不如我帮你做点什么
Why don't you let me make you something?
把你的新家打理一下
Maybe put this new place of yours in some kind of order.
让我干吧
Come on.
我欠你的
I owe you that much.
好吧 谢谢 警长
Okay. Thanks, Sheriff.
喊我乔迪
Jody.
你觉得会有那么简单吗
Did you think it would be that easy?
没有
No.
但这是个开始
But it's a start.
你没事吧
You okay?
要知道他们装成我们的样子
You know, it's bad enough that they're ganking people,
四处杀人就够可恶了
wearing our mugs,
现在又来这个
but now this?
让我们开着这辆…卡布德
Have us driving around in this…Caboodle.
却把我的爱车锁起来
while baby's on lockdown.
这都是暂时的 迪恩
It's temporary, Dean.
不能委屈我的爱车
Nobody puts baby in a corner.
这…这台词是…
Y-you know that's a line from …
斯威兹的电影（《终极豪情》中的抢劫犯） 斯威兹总能化险为夷
Swayze movie. Swayze always gets a pass!
没错
Right.
你想来点音乐什么的吗
Uh, well, you want some tunes or something?
- 抱歉 兄弟 我…我 - 让它放吧
- Sorry, man, I-I… - Just leave it.
可能就这么一首歌
Probably gonna be the only thing on.
- 迪恩 - 怎么
- Dean. - What?
耶利哥 白衣女鬼
Jericho … the lady in white.
黑水山脉 食人魔
Blackwater … wendigo.
曼莱托克湖 湖里的孩子
Lake Manitoc … the kid in the lake.
他们去的都是我们干过活的地方
They're hitting towns we've worked jobs in.
还是按顺序来的
In order.
从我跟着你离开斯坦福大学的那天起
Since the day I left Stanford with you.
什么情况 他们希望我们找到他们吗
So, what, they want us to find them?
有个证实的办法
Well, one way to find out …
下一件案子是在 圣路易斯
next case would be in…St. Louis.
太棒了 康纳餐馆
Perfect. Connor's Diner.
圣路易斯最好吃的汉堡
Best burgers in St. Louis.
我也该享受点生命中美好的事物了
Oh, I deserve something good in my life right now.
他每天都要吃一个这种东西
You know, he has one of these every day.
并且在他心里
And in his heart,
他觉得这些东西跟性爱一样美妙
he thinks they're almost as good as sex.
这东西
This…
真恶心
is disgusting.
死掉的植物还有奶油一样的黏状物
Dead plants with creamy goo.
就好像在吃自以为是
It's like eating self-righteousness.
你来告诉我哪件事更悲剧
I mean, you tell me which is worse.
说真的 我真是 你知道吗
I mean, honestly, I just… You know what?
我真受不了这家伙
I can't stand the guy.
还说什么英雄情结
Talk about a hero complex.
他连恋人都没有
And he doesn't have relationships.
不 他能去当圣徒了
No, he has applications for Sainthood.
还有他觉得自己很搞笑
Oh, and he thinks he's funny.
他觉得自己是郭德纲呢
He thinks he's a damn comedian.
疯癫二逼青年何处找
Who has two thumbs and full-blown bats in the belfry?
不开玩笑
I'm serious.
脑子里净是路西法的身影
It's nothing but Satan-vision on the inside.
真不明白他心里乱的魂肉都要分离了
I mean, how he's walking around in a jacket.
还怎么穿着这件夹克到处乱晃
with detachable arms is beyond me.
我曾有个兄弟也有这么多麻烦事
You know, I had a brother with this many issues once.
- 是吗 - 知道我干了什么吗
- Yeah? - Know what I did?
我吃了他
I ate him.
那是当然
Of course you did.
这些家伙怎么会是个威胁呢
How are these guys even a threat?
老大说他们得死 他们就得死
Boss says they gotta go, they gotta go.
没错
Right.
有个想法
Idea.
你想不想来交换一下
You wanna trade?
比起这疯子我宁可要搞笑的
I mean, I'll take chuckles over schizo.
不要 我更喜欢这家伙的头发
No, I like this one's hair better.
你还是待在你那个大家伙的身体里吧
You can stay in the big one.
好吧 既然如此 那我们就搞点动静出来
All right. In that case, let's turn up the heat.
我越早离开这躯壳找个更稳定的
The sooner I get out of this and into something more stable,
就越好
the better.
等等
Hold on.
小伙子
Hey, kid. Hey.
你不如打开那东西上的摄像头吧
Why don't you fire up the camera on that thing?
把它对准这里
Point it over here.
我们开始吧
Shall we?
大家都冷静点 我们是来抢劫的
All right, everybody be cool! This is a robbery!
有人动的话
Anybody moves,
我就杀光你们每一个人
and I'll execute every last one of you!
砍下他们的头杀不了他们
Choppin' their heads off won't kill 'em,
不过也能很有效地拖延他们了
but it'll slow 'em down pretty good.
不过头还会再粘回去
Till they fuse back up, anyhow.
也算是有点进展了
Well, that's something, I guess.
不过我们还未必能靠近他们
I mean, assuming we can even get close to them.
相信我 我也不想你们走到他们跟前去
Believe me, I don't want you walking right up to 'em, either.
我还在找你们能用来射杀他们的东西
I'm still looking for something you can shoot at 'em.
好时光啊 谢了 鲍比
Good times. All right, thanks, Bobby.
你吃蛋黄酱的对吧 鲍比
Hey, you take mayo, right, Bobby?
你那里有个小妞吗
You got a chick over there?
什么
What?
没有
No.
你在办事吗 理查德·基尔（好莱坞男演员）
Are you even working, Richard Gere?
闭嘴 你个白痴
Shut up, you idjit.
你们兄弟俩接着去哪里
Where are you boys off to next?
圣路易斯 那是我们
Uh, St. Louis. That's where we …
太晚了
It's too late.
他们去过圣路易斯了
They hit St. Louis.
洗劫了那里的一家餐馆
Pumpkin-and-Honeybunny'd a diner there.
康纳餐馆吗
Connor's Diner?
对 你怎么知道
Yeah. How'd you know?
随便猜猜
Lucky guess.
那就这样吧
All right, so much for that.
我想我们要去
I guess we're off to…
爱荷华州安克尼市
To Ankeny, Iowa.
如果你有所收获 打电话给我们
Call us if you get anything else.
知道了
You got it.
我们是莫瑞斯和瓦伦提特工
Special agents Morris, Valente.
你是最先到案发现场的吗
You were first on the scene?
很不幸 是的
Unfortunately.
要不要告诉我们发生了什么
Wanna tell us what happened?
把那东西拿好
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey! Keep that up!
我没说你能把它放下
I didn't say you could put that down!
我要让全世界都知道
I want the whole world to know.
萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特能做什么
what Sam and Dean Winchester are capable of.
杀光了吗
That all of 'em?
还差一个
All but one.
不要 拜托 不要
No, please, no.
晚安 圣路易斯
Well, goodnight, St. Louis.
你们真是棒极了
You've been a wonderful crowd.
爱荷华州的人们 快逃吧
Grab your socks and hose, Iowa,
我们接着就要朝你们那里去了
'cause we're headed to you next.
我们要警告
We need to alert …
联邦 州和当地警局 这就去
Federal, state, local … I'm on it.
这幅躯壳有没有让我看起来很胖
Does this skin make me look fat?
混蛋
Balls.
记忆挺晦暗啊
It's pretty dark in here.
高中辍学
High-school dropout.
有个酒鬼老爸
A drunk like your daddy before you.
你和你爸都是
Oh. You and dad.
真是一丘之貉
Now, that's a can of scorpions.
你最爱的歌手是琼尼·米歇尔吗
Your favorite singer is Joni Frickin' Mitchell?
鲍比
Oh, Bobby.
你的忧郁都要兜不住了
You are 10 pounds of sad in a 5-pound bag.
（安克尼旅馆）
萨姆 萨姆 站好别动
Sam, Sam. Hold up.
别动 别乱动
Don't move. Don't move.
别啊
Oh, no.
真是太过分了
This is all sorts of wrong.
那车可真不错
Those are nice wheels.
等事情结束了
Tell you what, when this is over,
我要把车偷过来
I'm stealing those rims.
跟孩子们问声好
Tell the kids I said hi.
喂
Yeah.
鲍比 我们找到他们了
Bobby, we got eyes on them.
什么
What?
简直像照镜子
It's like looking at a funhouse mirror.
我了解你的感受
Yeah, I know the feeling.
告诉我们你有收获了
All right, well, tell me you got something.
否则我们就要近身战了
Otherwise, we're gonna have to get in close.
听着 先原地等等
Look, just hang back for now.
太晚了 我们必须…
It's too late. We gotta …
等等
Hang on.
举起手来
Hands in the air!
你误会了
Big misunderstanding.
- 你们要抓的人 - 闭嘴
- Look, the guys you want - shut up!
- 他们就在那边 你们转过去 - 闭嘴
- they're right there. Just turn around. - Shut up!
- 看啊 - 放下电话 高举双手
- Look. - Drop the phone. Put your hands in the air.
迪恩
Dean?
Dean!
- 要说你啊 鲍比 - 闭嘴
- You know the thing about you, Bobby… - Save it.
我了解我自己 帅哥
I already know me, handsome.
你一副粗声粗气的样子
You got the gruff thing down.
见证了无数的死亡
Seen more death than an electric chair.
随时准备战死沙场
Ready to die with your boots on.
可是 在你的内心深处
But, you know, deep down inside…
你不是那么的愤世嫉俗
You're no cynic.
你还是有希望的
You still hope.
甚至对楼上的小姐还有点意思
You even got a thing for that lady upstairs.
你心里有那么一小块想着
Tiny part of you thinks,
也许
maybe…
等着一切都过去了
after this is all done,
你跟我们的警长小姐可以在树林深处
you and miss sheriff can make your own little cabin.
建个自己的房子
in the woods.
真是可笑
That's hilarious.
你连明天早上的太阳都看不到了 鲍比
You're not getting any older than tomorrow, Bobby.
何必费这个心呢
Why do you bother?
你喜欢勃朗宁的诗吗
You a Browning fan?
你说什么
Come again?
罗伯特·勃朗宁
Robert Browning.
诗人
Poet.
你没有在我的思维和情感中
You got that name rattling around up there.
看到他的名字吗
with the rest of my thoughts and feelings?
你总是醉得不省人事
It's kind of hard to sift through.
找东西可有点困难 不过…
all the drunken blackouts, but …
「人要追求自己得不到的东西」
"A man's reach should exceed his grasp."
我喜欢这句话
I like that.
听起来棒极了
That's actually lovely.
勃朗宁是吗
Browning?
等我吃了你
After I eat you,
我绝对会去图书馆看他的书
I'm definitely gonna hit the library.
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
把它弄掉
Get it off.
Get it off!
把它弄掉
Get it off!!
把它从我身上弄掉
Get it off of me!
Get it off me!
对不起 这儿有点小乱
Oh, sorry. Little snafu here.
这可真是意料之外
Okay, wasn't expecting that reaction.
水桶里边是什么东西
What the hell was in that bucket?
你们搞错了
Look, you're making a mistake.
真正的凶手还在餐厅里 懂吗
The real killers are back at the diner, okay?
这就是你无力的辩解吗
Is that the best you can do?
我要打电话
I want my phone call.
会有电话的 不过是给联调局的
Oh, there'll be a call, to the FBI.
把他关进一号囚室
Take him to cell number one.
带这个去审讯室
Take that one to the interview room.
把他们分开关好
Once they're separate and secure,
你们今晚就可以收工了
you boys call it a night.
你们弄错了
You're making a mistake!
你们俩忘了什么东西了吗
What, did you guys forget something or what?
（安克尼 警长办公室）
我有权打电话
Hey. I have a right to my phone call.
权利
A right?
你过去的几天杀了多少人
You killed how many people last couple days,
居然还敢让我来帮你实现权利
and you want me to hop-to on your rights?
我没有
I didn't …
拜托了
Please …
就让我打一个电话
Just give me one … one phone call.
孩儿们
Boys?
鲍比 我们被抓了
Bobby, we got popped.
好吧 我会马上过来的
Okay. I'll be there as soon as …
不用了 没时间 我们看到他们了
No, no, there's no time. Look, we saw them…
他们也看到我们
They saw us.
因此 「我们」要来找我们
So, we are coming to get us.
你懂了吗
You read me?
你有什么发现吗
Tell me you got something.
一种化学成分
There's a chemical …
硼酸钠
Sodium borate.
好吧 我要去问百度知道了
Okay, let me get Mr.Wizard on speed dial.
不 不 这挺靠谱的
No, no, it ain't as weird as it sounds.
化工清洁剂 肥皂还有洗衣粉
It's found in industrial cleaners and soaps.
里面都有
and laundry powder.
找那些带硼酸字样的产品就好
Just look for anything with the word borax on it.
你要我当绝望主妇对付这帮怪物吗
You want me to "Desperate Housewife" these mothers?
不是 相信我就对了
No, just trust me.
这东西能烧伤他们 足够拖延时间了
It burns 'em bad enough to slow 'em down.
找剂量最大的那种 懂了吗
So get the strongest you can find. Hear me?
硼酸 烧伤 懂了
Borax. Burns. Got it.
然后泼向他们
Then douse 'em,
靠近 砍下他们的脑袋
then get close, and then chop the heads off.
懂了
Got it.
把脑袋单独放置
And keep the heads separate!
鲍比 你是个天才 谢谢
Bobby, you're a genius. Thanks. I …
你干嘛挂电话
What'd you do that for?
硼酸 斩首
Borax? Decapitation?
你和你朋友都是些什么疯子啊
What kind of sickos are you and your friends?
听我说
Hey, you listen to me.
如果你不马上去把那东西
If you don't go get every ounce,
能找到的每一滴
every drop of whatever that stuff is.
都搜集来
in this place right now…
我们都会死的
We're all gonna die!
你比我想象的还疯
Well, you're crazier than I thought.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
你怎么回事
What is your problem?
现在可没时间吃饭
We don't have time for lunch right now.
我饿了
I was hungry.
等会的 快走
Later. let's go.
怎么了
What is it?
发生什么事了
What happened?
那个 我
I…it's just…
我不知道刚才看到的是什么
I don't know what I just saw.
放我出去
Let me out of here.
照我说的做 咱们都可以活下去
Okay, you listen to me, and we'll live.
悄悄地到补给柜子那去
All right, keep your head down, get to the supply closet.
拿来所有带有硼酸字样的物品
Get anything that says borax on it … bring it here.
快去吧
Now. go.
迪恩
Dean!
我不是你哥哥
I'm not your brother.
我近似迪恩
But I am Dean adjacent.
不好意思
Sorry.
小萨姆
Sammy.
不是小萨姆
Not sammy.
我只是想告诉你
I just want to let you know.
自从变成你们以来
How much I've really grown to hate.
我是越来越狠你俩了
you and your brother since we've been wearing you.
我不明白
I just don't get it.
你们前途无量
You could be anything.
强壮 无牵无挂
You're strong. You're uninhibited.
信不信由你 还挺聪明
You're smart enough, believe it or not.
但你们太在意做个好人
But you're so caught up in being good.
和照顾彼此了
and taking care of each other.
关你什么事
What do you care?
这让我生气
Because it pisses me off!
你浪费了一个绝佳的
You're wasting a perfectly good opportunity.
征服弱者的机会
to subjugate the weak.
真萌 你根本无法靠近我 怎么用得上那东西
Cute. Really think you can get close enough to use it?
你烧伤了我就能了
Not until you're burning.
是这么回事
Here's the deal.
迪恩
Dean…
认为你是个疯子
…thinks you're nutballs.
他认为你崩溃了
He thinks you're off your game.
你是想杀我吗 还是说
You gonna kill me, or is.
这是你所谓的 饭前消遣
this some sort of "play with your food" bull?
好吧
All right.
我想这就是为什么迪恩不告诉你
You know, I guess that's why dean never told you.
他杀了艾米
that he killed amy.
来了
There it is.
看看你那表情
The look on your face.
真是太完美了
That is priceless!
我就是等这个呢
That's what I've been waiting for.
现在我能吃你了
Now I can eat you.
因为呢
'Cause, you see,
我喜欢有点苦味的肉
I like my meat a little bitter.
这感觉不错
Well, that felt good.
那么
So…
联邦调查局正在赶来
The FBI is on the way.
那个 关于这个
Yeah, listen, about that…
不论你们要我做什么
Whatever I can do…
要我隐瞒刚刚发生的一切更不在话下
especially if it involves lying about everything I just saw.
不错
Good.
我只是希望你能让我们 死掉
I was hoping you could help us kind of… be dead.
打引号的那种
You know, quote unquote.
好的
Yeah.
好的 我应该可以做到
Yeah, I should be able to swing that.
好吧
All right.
走吧 拿拖把擦地了
Come on, let's grab a mop.
小萨姆 怎么了
Sammy? you okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
走吧
Let's go.
我就在这时先发制人
That's when I got the drop on them.
然后将他俩击毙
and shot them both.
你做的很好 警长
You did good, sheriff.
档案在这里
Here's the files.
死因 多处枪伤
Cause of death … multiple gunshot wounds.
当然了 我先采取了指纹
I fingerprinted them first, of course,
以便存档记录
for your records.
我们能看看尸体吗
Mind if we take a look at the bodies?
他们的尸体已经送殡仪馆火化了
Their bodies were sent to the funeral home for cremation,
这是他们的生前遗愿和宗教需要
as per their living wills and religious requirements.
这还真是效率
That must be some kind of record.
他们昨晚才死
They died last night.
你可以联系下殡仪馆
You can contact the funeral home.
他们没准还留着尸体
They might still have the bodies.
你知道 当做完尸检
As you know, once we do the autopsy,
我们就要释放
we're obliged to release …
你毁掉了尸体
You had the bodies destroyed?
你这算哪门子的暗箱操作啊
What kind of backwater operation is this?
别激动 算了吧
Easy. Forget about it.
没尸体 无报告 对吧
No bodies, no paperwork, right?
有人跟我说过这是件好事
Someone once told me that was a good thing.
好消息还是好消息
The good news still stands.
这案件结束了
This case is closed.
萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特死了
Sam and dean winchester are dead.
温彻斯特兄弟的杀人狂旅在爱荷华血腥终结
The winchester crime spree has come to a violent end in iowa,
两人皆被击毙
where they were gunned down.
这样就能消停一段日子了
That should take the heat off. For now.
谢了 乔迪
Thanks, Jody.
没你可真不行
Couldn't have done it without you.
再要我帮什么忙
Anytime you need me to spill something else,
打个电话就行了
you give me a call.
实际上 还有件事
Actually, there is one more thing.
别打开
Don't open it.
就算他说话也别
Even if it starts talking.
特别是他说话的时候
Especially if it starts talking.
当你路过山下的桥时
When you cross over underhill bridge,
扔到河里就行了
just toss it in the drink.
我得失陪了
If you'll excuse me,
我还要往水泥里埋一具尸体
I, um…I got a body to bury in cement.
爸爸 你不是吧
Dad, seriously?
向联邦调查局撒谎 焚化尸体
Lying to the FBI, incinerating bodies,
还有这玩意
and this stuff?
这是什么东西
What the hell is it?
因为这肯定不是血
'Cause it sure isn't blood.
你说得对 亲爱的
You're right about that, sweetie.
远不止血那么简单
It's much more than blood.
我可以解释
I can explain.
没必要
Don't bother.
我是瓦伦丁
It's Valente.
是 头儿 他们就在我手边
Yes, sir, I'm with them now.
不幸的是 他们的头…
Well, unfortunately, their heads are…
不见了
Missing.
- 真正的温家双煞死了 对吗 - 没有 头儿
- But the actual Winchesters are dead, yes? - No, sir.
他们跑路了
They're in the wind.
这么说 用了那么多人和资源
So, all that brainpower, all those resources,
那两只田鼠还逍遥在外吗
and those two field mice are still on my to-do list?
很抱歉 头儿
I'm sorry, sir.
拿到更多DNA后 再伪装成他们
We could grab some more DNA and double them again.
这想法不错
I like where your head's at,
不过有的计不能反复施
but sometimes less is more.
他们又死而复生
Those boys coming back from the dead again.
就难以让人相信了
starts to strain credulity,
即使美国媒体也会怀疑的 不是吗
even for the American media, am I right?
是的 头儿
Yes, sir.
行事要隐秘
I like a subtler approach.
此事须回正规
Back to the vision board on this one.
遵命
Of course.
保护好尸体 回联调局来
Just secure the bodies and get back to the FBI,
我们再议温家双煞一事
And we'll give this Winchester situation a good think.
一定的 谢谢 头儿
Definitely. Thanks, sir.
还有瓦伦提
And, Valente?
下次 我要听到好消息
Next time, call me with a win.
你好自为之
For your sake.
别逼我对你动手
Please don't make me bib you.
是的 头儿
Yes, sir.
我想喝拿铁
I'm craving a Latte.
你能去街对面买杯来
You mind running across the street.
然后我们再出发
before we hit the trail?
无咖啡因 双份香草
Decaf, two pumps of vanilla,
你自己也随便买点 我请客
and grab yourself whatever you want … my treat.
罗曼先生
Mr. Roman.
我想是时候来见见你了
I felt it was time we met in person.
我是克劳力
I'm Crowley.
地狱之主
I run hell.
是的 当然 我完全同意
Yes, yes. Of course. I agree, 100%.
是该见见了
High time we met.
不成敬意
A token.
太客气了
You shouldn't have.
我喜欢松糕
I love a muffin.
纯有机婴儿小舌
100% organic baby uvulas …
不含麸质
Gluten free.
太周到了
So considerate.
我就开门见山了 罗曼先生
I'll cut to the chase, Mr. Roman.
请叫我迪克
Please. Dick.
迪克
Dick.
你我各自掌控着极大利益
You and I control large interests.
我坚信可以强强联合
that I feel strongly could meld,
从此皆大欢喜
to the benefit of all.
- 你这么想吗 - 我确定
- You think? - I know.
坦率说 我们应当成为朋友
Straight talk … we should be friends,
我和你
You and I.
为什么
Why?
我们为什么该做朋友呢
Why in the world would we be?
是我把你带到这里
Well, I brought you here…
迪克
Dick.
我找到了打开炼狱之门的办法
I found the way to open the door to purgatory.
你是为了窃取那里的灵魂
To steal every last soul, you mean.
你和你那个天使朋友
You and that angel friend of yours.
别一边忽悠我 还说是为了我好
Don't roofie me and call it romance.
你误解我了
I think you've got me wrong.
现在你给我听着
Now it's your turn to listen.
我宁愿在垃圾堆里打滚
I'd sooner swim through hot garbage.
也不要和你这种下贱的怪物握手言和
than shake hands with a bottom-feeding mutation like you.
你们恶魔都是丑陋 懒惰 拜金的婊子
You demons are ugly, lazy, gold-digging whores.
你们还不如人类
You're less than humans,
而他们也只有蘸着蒜酱
and they're not good for much.
才算有点用处
till you dip 'em in garlic sauce.
我永远不会跟你合作 克劳力
I'd never work with you, Crowley.
事实上 如果我不是忙着做其他事
In fact, if I wasn't busy with better things,
我就把你们从宇宙中彻底消灭
I might actively wipe your kind from the face of the universe.
那样也是你们活该
And you'd deserve it.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
松糕留着吃吧
Keep the muffins.
你确定要把这些丢掉吗
Are you sure you want to dump these things?
我估计后面说不定能派上用场呢
I'm thinking they might actually come in handy down the road.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
你怎么了 什么事 说啊
What? What is it? Talk.
没什么
Nothing.
你指望我信吗
Well, that's convincing.
怪物版的我们把你吓傻了吗
Did monster-us give you the jeebs, huh?
老实说
'Cause I gotta be honest …
我可得有日子不去照镜子了
I ain't looking in the mirror for … for a while myself.
好吧
Okay.
你真想知道我哪里不对劲吗
You really want to know what's wrong?
对
Yeah.
对 你知道我的座右铭 为人民服务
Yeah, you know my motto … here to help.
「为人民服务」
"Here to help."
那你是怎么对艾米的
Kind of like you helped Amy?
听我说 萨姆
Listen, Sam…
别…别再对我撒谎了
Don't … don't lie to me again.
不 别再跟我讲话了
No, don't even talk to me.
我不能
Yeah, I can't.
迪恩 我做不到
You know what, Dean? I can't.
你做不到什么
You can't what?
我现在不能跟你讲话
I can't talk to you right now!
迪恩 我现在甚至不能跟你呆在一起
Dean, I can't even be around you right now!
好吧 那…
Okay, so …
那你还是一个人走吧
So I think you should just go on without me.
走
Go.
好吧
All right.
抱歉 萨姆
Sorry, Sam.